{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application. hdhdfhd",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Qwerty",
      "description": "This is a test deck. I'm updating this!",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "lipton ice teajkjijojoj",
      "description": "A history of tea makingdagfdfasfa",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "One more test Deck",
      "description": "I'm testing this one out to make sure this works correctly",
      "id": 5
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "This is a new card",
      "back": "Creating a new card",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "This is a test",
      "back": "For the test",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "This is a new card for fun",
      "back": "Testing purposes",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "This is a new card that I want to test",
      "back": "It's right!",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "hello",
      "back": "world",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "hello.ghdfh. This finally works",
      "back": "how are you. boo!",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "Testing this card creation",
      "back": "this is a new card",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "this is a new card",
      "back": "wanjfkjnfa",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "let's see",
      "back": "let's see about this",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "this is DONE!!!!",
      "back": "Finished!!!!!",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 18
    }
  ]
}